♪ under the cover of l'obscurité, in le vide of Shattered mémoire-Glass, desperate.
Lyra: Got it!
Lyra: Almost gone...
Lyra: Mine. Now.
♪ under the cover of l'obscurité, in Crumbling mémoire-Platform, tense.
Lyra: Urgh! Hard landing!
Echo Shard: Unnecessary struggle.
Lyra: Not yet!
♪ under the cover of l'obscurité, in Crumbling mémoire-Platform, urgent.
Lyra: Stay back!
Kael: Hold it... tight.
Echo Shard: Worthless fragment.
Lyra: jamais worthless.
♪ at dawn, in Collapsing mémoire-Corridor Entrance, desperate.
Lyra: Falling apart!
Lyra: non... not that one!
Echo Shard: Release the pain.
Lyra: Gone...
♪ at dawn, in Loom's Constricting Corridor, urgent.
Lyra: Can't breathe!
Kael: Push... Lyra.
Lyra: Not here. Not now!
Loom of Oblivion: Submission. Inevitable.
♪ at dawn, in Nursery of Dormant souvenirs, dread.
Lyra: What is this?
Loom of Oblivion: A haven. Preservation.
Lyra: They're... sleeping?
Loom of Oblivion: Protected. From you.
♪ at dawn, in Nursery of Dormant souvenirs, tense.
Lyra: Kael... non.
Kael: Too close... Lyra.
Lyra: It hurts...
Loom of Oblivion: Relinquish the burden.
♪ at dawn, in Nursery of Dormant souvenirs, urgent.
Lyra: sors!
Lyra: Not my souvenirs!
Loom of Oblivion: Foolish resistance.
Lyra: Almost there!
♪ at dusk, in Edge of a mémoire-Chasm, desperate.
Lyra: Dead end!
Loom of Oblivion: Nowhere left.
Lyra: Is this it?
Kael: Think... Lyra.
♪ at dusk, in Chasm's Edge, desperate.
Lyra: non choice!
Lyra: It burns!
Kael: rappelle-toi... me.
Lyra: Jump!
♪ at dusk, in Across the Chasm / Loom's Projection, dread.
Lyra: Made it!
Loom of Oblivion: We knew you would.
Lyra: What?
Loom of Oblivion: Your path is clear. To us.